question_data = [
{
"type": "boolean",
"difficulty": "easy",
"category": "General Knowledge",
"question": "Vietnam&#039;s national flag is a red star in front of a yellow background.",
"correct_answer": "False",
"incorrect_answers": [
"True"
]
},
{
"type": "boolean",
"difficulty": "easy",
"category": "General Knowledge",
"question": "Jingle Bells was originally meant for Thanksgiving",
"correct_answer": "True",
"incorrect_answers": [
"False"
]
},
{
"type": "boolean",
"difficulty": "easy",
"category": "General Knowledge",
"question": "The Lego Group was founded in 1932.",
"correct_answer": "True",
"incorrect_answers": [
"False"
]
},
{
"type": "boolean",
"difficulty": "easy",
"category": "General Knowledge",
"question": "Is a dog a mammal?",
"correct_answer": "True",
"incorrect_answers": [
"False"
]
},
{
"type": "boolean",
"difficulty": "easy",
"category": "General Knowledge",
"question": "French is an official language in Canada.",
"correct_answer": "True",
"incorrect_answers": [
"False"
]
},
{
"type": "boolean",
"difficulty": "easy",
"category": "General Knowledge",
"question": "Adolf Hitler was born in Australia. ",
"correct_answer": "False",
"incorrect_answers": [
"True"
]
},
{
"type": "boolean",
"difficulty": "easy",
"category": "General Knowledge",
"question": "The Sun rises from the North.",
"correct_answer": "False",
"incorrect_answers": [
"True"
]
},
{
"type": "boolean",
"difficulty": "easy",
"category": "General Knowledge",
"question": "The color orange is named after the fruit.",
"correct_answer": "True",
"incorrect_answers": [
"False"
]
},
{
"type": "boolean",
"difficulty": "easy",
"category": "General Knowledge",
"question": "The National Animal of Scotland is the Unicorn.",
"correct_answer": "True",
"incorrect_answers": [
"False"
]
},
{
"type": "boolean",
"difficulty": "easy",
"category": "General Knowledge",
"question": "&quot;27 Club&quot; is a term used to refer to a list of famous actors, musicians, and artists who died at the age of 27.",
"correct_answer": "True",
"incorrect_answers": [
"False"
]
}
]